better.org.uk 2016-05-24

# Better: The Feel Good Place. Find a centre today.

We respect each individual’s right to personal privacy ("you"/"your"). We will collect and use information through our website only in the ways covered in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected on our website [www.better.org.uk](http://www.better.org.uk/) and [www.gll.org](http://www.gll.org/) ("our website(s)").

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 ("Act"), the data controller is Greenwich Leisure Ltd ("we"/"our"/"us") of Middlegate House, 1 Seymour Street, Woolwich, London SE18 6SX. Our nominated representative for the purposes of the Act is Philip Donnay.

### Information we may collect about you

We collect information through our website at several points. We may collect and process the following information about you: 

  * information submitted through enquiry forms, newsletter subscription forms and information that you provide when filling in any other forms on our site; 
  * details of your visit to our website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data and the resources you access; and 
  * personally identifiable information which you provide about other people, such as referrals or subscriptions. 

We do not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child to reveal personal information.

### Cookies

We use cookies for website statistic analysis. A cookie is a small text file that our web server places on your computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable us to track usage patterns and deliver customised content to our users. Our cookies do not have an expiration date and do not collect personally identifiable information. 

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be to access all or parts of our website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon you visit our website.

### What we may use your information for

The information collected by us will be used for statistical and internal marketing purposes and so as to ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for your and your computer.

If you provide us with specific information, and at your request, you may receive email announcements, news updates or other specifically requested information. 

### Disclosure of your information 

We share your information with third parties where we manage their facilities. This might include a local authority or a company. The information will be disclosed to provide the services you have requested, contact you about your membership and may be used to send you information about other services we or our Partner Organisations think will be of interest to you.

We may disclose your information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your information in the event that we sell or buy any business assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

### Links

From time to time we may offer links to other web sites. Please note, when you click on links to other websites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours and we do not accept responsibility or liability for their policies.

### Changes to our privacy policy

We may review our privacy policy at any time by updating this page. You are expected to check back from time to time to take notice of any changes we have made, as they are binding on you.

### Your rights

You have a right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise this right at any time by contacting us.

### Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right to access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

### Contact

If problems arise, please [contact us here](http://www.gll.org/b2b/contact) or at the address given above. We are committed to resolving disputes as soon as possible.
